Kimberley Yung

Digital & Social Media Marketer/Software Engineer

Contact

Address:

Scarborough, ONTARIO, M1T3W7

Phone:

(437) 329 2868

E-mail:

kyung.97@hotmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kimberleyyung/

Website:

https://kimberleyyung.me/

Languages

English Mandarin Cantonese

Profile

Social Media Marketer and Software Engineer with over 5 years of experience in web-based applications, social networking, blogging, and online advertising. Extensive knowledge of web technologies and current social media platforms. Successfully assesses client's needs, generating options and implementing solutions for social media.

Experience

October 2022—Present Software Engineer(Intern) GET-TECH Solutions Toronto, ON, Canada

January 2022—January 2023 Sales Representative Rainbow Jade

Toronto, ON, Canada

January 2020—November 2021

Graphics Designer/Website Designer/Social Media

Marketer

Self Employed Services

Melbourne, VIC, Australia

Febuary 2017—March 2021

Sales Supervisor/Business Specialist

Optus (Masterlink)

Melbourne, VIC, Australia

January 2014—January 2021

Graphics Designer/Website Designer

Amplify Group Pty Ltd

Melbourne, VIC, Australia

Key Skills

Print media expertise
Social media networking
Graphics design
Product demonstrations
Customer satisfaction
Upselling strategies
Product promotions
Merchandising
Sales orientation
Cash Handling
Point of sale operation
Content Marketing
Search Engine Optimization
Marketing Automation Software
HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Education

January 2022 - Current

Diploma: Software Engineering Technician

Toronto, ON, Canada Centennial College

April 2020 - April 2021

Diploma: Digital and Social Media Marketing

Melbourne, VIC, Australia Australian Pacific College

January 2016 - January 2017

Diploma: Design and Visual Communication

Melbourne, VIC, Australia Swinburne University